markmeldrum.com 2019-01-21

# Privacy Policy – Mark Meldrum, Ph.D.

**MarkMeldrum.com Privacy Policy**

_Last updated:_ June 18, 2018

2533695 Ontario Limited operating as MarkMeldrum.com is a Limited Liability Corporation which supports CFA© candidates in mastering content for Levels I, II and III. As a CFAI-Approved Prep Provider, we are located at 210 Martindale Road in St. Catharines Ontario Canada, and we own and operate this website (the ‘Site’).

This privacy policy ( **‘Privacy Policy’** ):

  * Describes how we gather and protect personal information ( **‘Personal Information’** )
  * How we use and share Personal Information

**Personal Information**

We do collect some personal information from you, as you can imagine it is important to us to know where our candidates live (in order to plan seminars and online events accessible in every time zone) and how to reach them by email (regarding account and payment issues). The information we collect, however, is never sold. We have no third party advertising affiliations and your content will never be data mined, lent, sold or otherwise manipulated for another organization’s benefit.

We use [Stripe](https://stripe.com/ca) for all online payments; their [privacy policy](https://stripe.com/ca/privacy) should be reviewed by our subscribers. We do not store any payment information on our website in any format whatsoever. Period.

If you request to have your account deleted, we are happy to oblige you. Please understand that there is no restore capability, so the **process is permanent**.

**Cookies**

_Not just for eating._

We do offer cookies to enhance the user experience, for example, to store your login information or to bookmark where you left off in a video on your learning device. These are the only cookie functionalities we offer, as what you do on your time is entirely none of our business. We just want you to enjoy your experience at markmeldrum.com.

**Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information**

You may view your Personal Information on file with us at any time by visiting Your Account ([LINK HERE](https://www.markmeldrum.com/members/jennymarkmeldrum-com/settings/)) on the markmeldrum.com website.  You may change some of your Personal Information, but please note that we may require additional information to authenticate your identity. ** **

**Changes to This Policy**

Except where limited by applicable law, we reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices by prominently posting notice of the update on this Site, and, when required, obtaining your consent. Any updates will become effective immediately after posting the updates to this Policy.

It is the subscriber’s responsibility to review this Policy periodically. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the “Last Updated” date above. You are free to decide whether or not to accept a modified version of this Policy, however your acceptance of this Policy is required for you to continue using the Site.

If we make any changes, to this Policy that materially and adversely impacts previously collected information about you, we will obtain your prior express consent for processing information previously collected about you in such a manner.

Questions? Email [mark@markmeldrum.com](mailto:mark@markmeldrum.com)and we’d be glad to help. By the way, I farted while writing this.
